Finding Aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) photograph series D (faculty and staff portraits), 1946-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
News and Information Services (University of Michigan) photograph series D (faculty and staff portraits) 1946-2006 1950-1990
University of Michigan. News and Information Services.
87265 Bimu C475 2
The University of Michigan News and Information Services functions as the university's media relations office. It disseminates information and images about university programs, research, events, and faculty and staff activities. This series of News and Information Services photographs is comprised of portraits of more than 4,000 individual faculty and staff members spanning the years 1946-2006 (bulk 1950-1990).
7.5 linear feet in 15 boxes
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
University of Michigan News and Information Services (donor no. 285) periodically deposits its photographs with the library. 285
No further additions to Series D, faculty portraits are expected.
The Series "D" faculty portraits are open without restriction.
The University of Michigan News and Information Services is responsible for preparing press releases about university activities, providing photographs and film of university functions and scholarly announcements to the various news media, and publishing and distributing the University Record and Michigan Today.
News and Information Services has undergone several name and organizational changes throughout its history. Beginning in 1897, the university had a department of information services that performed many of the functions of a press office. In 1930, following the installation of President Alexander G. Ruthven, the university created a News Dissemination Service (often called the University of Michigan News Service). Over the ensuing decades the name of the organization has changed from News Service to Information Services, and finally to News and Information Services. The organizational home of the unit has also changed as it moved from an independent unit to part of the Bureau of Alumni Relations, and later part of the Office of University Relations. It currently is part of the Vice President for Communications.
This series, commonly known as "Series D" is part of the News and Information Services photographs collection, which consists of several other series often based on format such as the size of the negatives (4x5 or 35mm) or content (general campus photography or aerial photographs). Series D consists of black and white 4x5 inch negatives and 1-1/4 x 2-1/4 inch prints and negatives of faculty and staff (and some student) portraits alphabetically arranged.
A comprehensive index for the entire series was created in 2007. It replaces what had been a partial index covering less than half of the content (two additions were received after the initial index was prepared). Based on information supplied on the original envelopes, the listing includes faculty/staff name, department or unit (when provided) and date(s) of the portrait. Bentley Library negative numbers are included (if applicable).
Summary Contents List
Series D (Faculty and Staff Portraits)
Box 1 -- A -- Berman
Box 2 -- Bernard -- Carr
Box 3 -- Carrick -- Dernberger
Box 4 -- Deskins -- Forman
Box 5 -- Forsyth -- Harris, Norman
Box 6 -- Harris, Patricia Roberts -- Johnson, Clyde
Box 7 -- Johnson, Harold --Lethstein
Box 8 -- Leiblee -- McKeachie
Box 9 -- McKean -- Nilsen
Box 10 -- Nisbet -- Pott
Box 11 -- Potter -- Schindler
Box 12 -- Schlatter-- Spink
Box 13 -- Spitzer -- Tyler
Box 14 -- Uberol -- Wikelund
Box 15 -- Wild -- Zygert
Subjects - Visual Materials:
University of Michigan--Employees--Portraits.; University of Michigan--Faculty--Portraits.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Series D, Faculty and Staff Portraits
  - A
    - Abbey, Stuart, Community Services, University Relations, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Abbot, Waldo, Speech, 1952 (Box 1)
    - Abbott, Nancy, Center for Continuing Education of Women, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Abbrecht, Peter, Physiology; Bioengineering, 1967, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Abdou, Saad El-Dine Ibrahim (Box 1)
      (na 14)
    - Abel, Richard, PTP, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Aberback, Public Administration, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Aberle, David F., 1960 (Box 1)
    - Ackermann, Wilbur, Epidemiology, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Ackley, Gardner, Economics, 1954, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Adams, David K., Electrical Engineering, 1961 (Box 1)
    - Adams, Henry C. II, Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Adams, James P., 1947 (Box 1)
      (na 16)
    - Adams, John, 1951 (Box 1)
    - Adams, Robert, Business Administration, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Adams, Thomas, School of Business Administration, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Adamson, Quin, Dance, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Adamson, Thomas C., Aeronautical Engineering, 1961, 1960, 1971, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Adelman, Richard, Institute of Gerontology; Medical School, 1983 (Box 1)
    - Adiv, Aaron, Urban Planning, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Aga-Oglu, Kamer Mrs., Museum of Anthropology, 1951 (Box 1)
    - Agranoff, Bernard, Medical School, 1967, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Aigler, Ralph W., Law, 1950 (Box 1)
    - Aiton, Arthur S., History (Box 1)
    - Akcasu, Ziya, Nuclear Engineering, 1963, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Ake, Christopher, 1966 (Box 1)
      (nb 10)
    - Akerman, Joseph R., Mechanical Engineering, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Albaladejo, Jose M., Spanish (Box 1)
      (na 19)
    - Albano, Joseph F., Architecture, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Albert, Edythe, WUOM, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Albright, William H., 1978, 1977, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Aleinikoff, Alex, Law, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Alexander, Carlton G., Naval Science, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Alexander, Florence, Hospital Administration, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Alexander, Paul, History, 1960, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Alexander, Paul, Mrs. (Box 1)
    - Alexander, Richard, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Alexander, Richard D., Zoology, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Alexander, William, English, 1995, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Alfred, Richard l., School of Education, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Allen, Francis A., Law, 1966, 1980, 1973, 1970, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Allen, Harold F., UMRI; Aeronautical and Astronautical Engineering, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Allen, James (Box 1)
    - Allen, John M., Zoology, 1966, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Allen, Leslie, First woman cadet in the ROTC, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Allen, Shirley, Forestry, 1956 (Box 1)
      (na 20)
    - Allen, Wendell, Affirmative Action Office, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Allen, Wyeth, Industrial Engineering, 1962, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Allen-Meares, Paula, Social Work, 1992, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Alley, John, Broadcasting Service, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Allison, Alexander W., Asst. to the Secretary of the University; English, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Allmand, Charles M., Business Administration; VP Academic Affairs, 1959, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Allnutt, Alvin, Naval Science, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Allyn, James, 1971 (Box 1)
    - Alm, Barbara L., Business Administration (Box 1)
    - Almuti, Amin M., Civil Engineering, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Alpern, Mathew, Ophthalmology; Physiology; Psychology, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Alston, William P., Philosophy, 1958 (Box 1)
    - Alt, Glenn L., Civil Engineering, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Altucher, Nathan, Psychology; Bureau of Psychological Services, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Alvord, Herbert H., Mechanical Engineering, 1954, 1971 (Box 1)
    - Ampulski, Gary, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Anderegg, Fred, 1951 (Box 1)
    - Andersen, Weggo, University Club, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Austin G., Continuing Legal Education, 1982, 1991, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Darrell, Bureau of Industrial Relations, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Dave, Housing, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, David B., Engineering, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Eddie, Resource Policy and Administration, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Irving, Education, 1976, 1961 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Judith, 1958 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Leigh C., Chemistry, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Lester, Education, 1967, 1959, 1954, 1971 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Major Gen., 1948 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Robert E., Health Service, 1974, 1967, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Ronald S., Education, 1956 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Samuel, Business Administration, 1955 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Theresa S., Extension Service, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Anderson-Imbert, Enrique, Spanish and Spanish American Literature, 1958 (Box 1)
      (na 23-24)
    - Andrews, Ann S., Psychology, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Andrews, Daniel L., Extension Service, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Andrews, Frank, ISR, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Andrews, Julia W., Art, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Andrews, Richard, Natural Resources, 1973, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Angell, Robert, Sociology, 1952, 1958 (Box 1)
    - Angell, Sarah Caswell, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Anning, Norman H., Math (Box 1)
      (na 42)
    - Anthony, Ann T., English Language Institute, 1964 (Box 1)
      (nb 23-25)
    - Anthony, Edward M., Jr., English Language Institute (Box 1)
    - Anthony, Yvonne, Affirmative Action, 1981 (Box 1)
    - Anton, Saul (SEE: Hopwood Winners), Hopwood Winner (Box 1)
    - Antonucci, Toni, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Aparicio, Frances, American Culture, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Appasamy, Paul, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Appel, Arthur, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Arden, Bruce, Computer and Communication Sciences, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Ardis, Evart W., Education; Career Planning and Placement, 1960, 1965, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Ardis, James B., Business Administration, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Arecheka, Dora, Markely Hall, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Arendt, Hannah (Box 1)
    - Aris, L. Lynnwood, Business Administration, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Arkland, Ezra H., Naval Science, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Armbruster, Edward, Public Health Engineering, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Armstrong, Robert L., Engineering Mechanics, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Arnett, Harold, Accounting, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Arnold, Chester A., Botany and Geology; Museum of Paleontology, 1959, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Arnold, Chunie, Art, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Arnold, Dean, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Arnold, Keith, School of Natural Resources, 1965, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Arnold, Richard, Electrical Engineering, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Arpaci, Vedat S., Mechanical Engineering, 1960, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Arroyo, Art, Sr. Sec. Literary Ad, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Arthos, John, English, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Asciutto, Michael (SEE: Hopwood Winners), Hopwood Winner (Box 1)
    - Ashe, Arthur, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Ashton, Robert, 1955 (Box 1)
    - Atiya, Near Eastern Studies (Box 1)
    - Atkins, Curt, Housing, 1996 (Box 1)
    - Atkins, Daniel, Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1972, 1990, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Atkins, Thomas M., Engineering Graphics, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Atkinson, John William, Pysch, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Atreya, Arvind, M.E.A.M., 1993 (Box 1)
    - Atreya, Sushil K., Atmos. And Oceanic Science, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Attwood, Madge, Education, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Atzmon, Michael, Physics, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Audas, William, Career Planning and Placement, 1975, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Augenstein, Joseph C., Personnel Office, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Aupperle, Eric, Engineering, 1983, 1962, 1968, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Austin, Carolyn, 1956 (Box 1)
      (na 46)
    - Austin, Douglas, Business Administration, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Austin, Henry R., Speech, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Avery, James K., Oral Biology (Box 1)
    - Awkward, Michael, English, 1986 (Box 1)
    - Axelrod, Morris, ISR, 1955 (Box 1)
    - Axelrod, Pearl G., Education, 1974, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Axelrod, Robert, Political Science, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Axelrod, Solomon, Public Health Economics, 1963, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Axsom, Richard, Art History, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Ayal, Eliezer B., Economics, 1961 (Box 1)
    - Ayers, John C., Zoology, 1961 (Box 1)
  - B
    - Baad, David W., Dean of Men, 1957 (Box 1)
      (na 50)
    - Babcock, Mellissa, Chemical Engineering, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Babcock, R. Gordon, Bureau of Industrial Relations, 1966, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Bach, David R., Nuclear Engineering, 1964, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Bachman, Jerald G., Survey Research Center, 1962, 1971, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Bacon, Deborah, Dean, 1951, 1954, 1961 (Box 1)
    - Bacon, Frank R., Jr., Institute of Science and Technology, 1964, 1962 (Box 1)
      (nb 47)
    - Bader, Arno L., English, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Bagozzi, Richard, Business Administration, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Bahor, Raymond, Institute of Industrial Health, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Baic, Dusan, Institute of Science and Technology; Zoology, 1964, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Baier, Louis Arthur, Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 1958 (Box 1)
    - Bailey, Frederic N., Electrical Engineering, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Bailey, Richard, English, 1968, 1993, 1976, 1983 (Box 1)
    - Bailey, Roger, Architecture, 1947 (Box 1)
      (na 59-61)
    - Baily, Reeve, Zoology, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Baird, Claribel, Speech, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Baker, Burton L., 1947 (Box 1)
    - Baker, Dean, Journalism, 1964, 1953, 1957, 1977, 1972 (Box 1)
      (na 54-55)
    - Baker, Deane, Regent, 1973, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Baker, Dennis, Engineering, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Baker, Georgianne, ISR, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Baker, Gwendolyn C., Education, 1978, 1976, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Baker, Lisa, University Relations, 1994, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Baker, Randy, Housing, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Baker, Sheridan W., Jr., English Language and Literature, 1969, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Bakker, Willem, Industrial and Operation Engineering, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Bald, F. Clever, History, 1949, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Baldwin, DeWitt C., Religious Affairs, 1959, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Baldwin, John W., History, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Ball, Deborah, Education (Box 1)
    - Ballence, Ann (Box 1)
    - Ballert, Albert G., Great Lakes Commission, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Ballinger, David, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Ballinger, Malcolm, University Hospital, 1956 (Box 1)
    - Ballis, William B., Political Science, 1966, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Balzhiser, Richard E., Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1969, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Banciu, Charles, Education, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Banfield, Ralph W., Naval Science, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Banks, Ted, 1950 (Box 1)
      (na 65-72, na 57)
    - Baraga, Frederic (Box 1)
      (na 62)
    - Barbarin, Oscar, Social Work, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Barber, Donald, Environmental Health, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Barber, Sue, WUOM, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Bardach, John E., Natural Resources, 1962, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Bardwick, Judith M., Psychology, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Barenberg, Sumner, Chemical Engineering, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Barkauskas, Violet H., Nursing, 1994, 1987, 1983, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Barker, Earnest, Physics, 1954 (Box 1)
      (na 73)
    - Barker, H. Kenneth, Bureau of Appointments and Occupational Information, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Barkin, Elaine, Music, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Barland, Edward, Naval Science, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Barnes, Burton, Forestry, 1965, 1969, 1980, 1994, 1987, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Barnes, Cyril H., Graphic Design, Eng., 1974 (Box 1)
    - Barnes, Samuel, Political Science, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Barnes, William Sprague, Comparative Law, 1949 (Box 1)
      (na 74-76)
    - Barnett, Norman E., Institute of Science and Technology, 1961, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Barney, Jane, Institute of Gerontology, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Baromeo, Chase, Voice, 1934 (Box 1)
      (na 251)
    - Baroway, Malcolm, State and Community Relations, 1980, 1982 (Box 1)
    - Barr, Donald, Education, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Barrett, Marjorie, Bentley, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Barrett, Michael (SEE: Hopwood Winners), Hopwood Winner (Box 1)
    - Barrett, Ralph P., English Language Institute, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Barritt, Loren, Education, 1972, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Barry, Alexander, Anatomy, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Barry, Elizabeth, OGC, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Barss, Joseph (Box 1)
      (na 78)
    - Bartels, Robert C. F., Math, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Barth, William P., Center for Research on Conflict Resolution, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Barthelemy, Felix, Medical Center, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Bartman, Frederick L. W., Aeronautical and Astronautical Engineering, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Barton, Ben F., Electrical Engineering, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Bartscht, Karl, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Bashshur, Rashid, Bureau of Public Health Economics, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Bass, Hyman, Math, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Bassett, Edward, Journalism, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Bassett, John R., Forestry; Natural Resources, 1977, 1975, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Bassett, Leslie, Music, 1973, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Bates, Marston, Zoology, 1952, 1955 (Box 1)
    - Batra, R., Business School, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Battles, Ron, Law, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Baum, John, Environmental Health, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Baxter, Dow V. (Box 1)
      (na 84-90)
    - Bayha, Franklin, Industrial Systems Research Laboratory, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Baylis, Janet, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Bayliss, George V., Art, 1978, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Be Ment, Spencer, Electrical Engineering, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Beach, Lowell W., Education, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Beagan, Bill, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Bean, James, Industrial and Operations Engineering, 1986 (Box 1)
    - Bean, John W. (Box 1)
    - Beardsley, Richard K. (Richard King), 1918-1978, Anthropology; Center for Japanese Studies, 1970, 1978, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Beattie, Kay, Office of the President, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Beaty, David, Engineering Mechanics, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Beaudry, Kenneth, Engineering Services (Box 1)
    - Beaven, Winton H., 1951 (Box 1)
      (na 120)
    - Beaver, Frank, Communication, 1987, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Becerra, Servio, Spanish, 1979, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Becher, Eric, Marching Band, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Becher, William, Electrical Engineering, 1971, 1978 (Box 1)
    - Becker, Alton L., English, College of Engineering, 1961, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Beckett, Morley, Public Health, 1963 (Box 1)
      (na 111)
    - Beckley, Robert, Architecture, 1965, 1990, 1987 (Box 1)
    - Beckwith, George C., 1953 (Box 1)
    - Bedell, Carolyn, Nursing, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Bedford, Neal, WUOM/WVGR, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Beecher, Robert W., State-wide Education; Business Manager, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Beeman, Alice, 1951, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Beeuwkes, Adelia, Public Health Nutrition, 1963, 1958, 1960 (Box 1)
      (na 97, na 119)
    - Behrman, Samuel J., Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Belcher, Jerry, News Service, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Bell, Earl J., University Musical Society, 1982, 1976, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Bell, Harold, Comptroller, 1958 (Box 1)
    - Bell, Margaret, Hygiene and Physical Education, 1953 (Box 1)
    - Bellaire, Frank R., Meterology; Engineering Mechanics, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Belsma, Alfred, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Bender, Jack E., Speech, 1961, 1951, 1969 (Box 1)
      (na 105)
    - Bender, Leonard F., Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1958, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Bender, Maurice, Natural Resources, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Bender, William, Medical Center, 1950, 1961, 1966, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Benedict, Milbry E. (Moby), Physical Education, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Benford, Harry, Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Bennet, James, Electrical Engineering, 1964 (Box 1)
    - Bennett, Charles Tanner (Box 1)
      (Bennet, Stewart)
    - Bennett, Donald R., Pharmacology, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Bennett, Edith, Survey Research Center (Box 1)
    - Bennett, Martha, Housing, 1985 (Box 1)
    - Bennett, Wells I., 1949 (Box 1)
    - Benninghoff, William, Natural Sciences, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Bentley, Alvin M., Regent, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Bentley, Norma F., Board in Control of Intercollegiate Athletics, 1960 (Box 1)
    - Bentley, William R., Natural Resources, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Berenson, Red, Sports Information, 1984 (Box 1)
    - Berg, Glen, Civil Engineering, 1965 (Box 1)
    - Berger, Andrew, Anatomy, 1963, 1962 (Box 1)
    - Berger, Carl F., Education, 1987, 1979, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Bergman, Floyd, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Bergmann, Frithjof H., Philosophy, 1965, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Bergsma, Ralph, Landscape Architecture, 1966 (Box 1)
    - Berkeley, Richard W., Industrial Engineering, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Berkhofer, Robert F., History, 1977 (Box 1)
    - Berlin, Byron S., Epidemiology, 1963 (Box 1)
    - Berlin, Lawrence, Extension Service, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Berman, Alex, Chemistry-Pharmacy, 1957 (Box 1)
    - Berman, William H., Law, 1958 (Box 1)
    - Bernard, Kent, Track coach, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Bernard, Sydney, Social Work, 1967, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Berndt, Louise A., Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Bernini, Georgio, Law, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Bernstein, Richard B., Chemistry, 1958 (Box 2)
    - Berry, Dean F., Business Administration, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Berry, Elmer G., Zoology, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Berry, Ralph Moore, Civil Engineering, 1960 (Box 2)
      (na 107-110)
    - Berry, Wallace T., Music, 1962, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Bertcher, Harvey, Social Work, 1964, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Berv, Harry, Business Administration; Music, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Besselink, Herman, 1955 (Box 2)
    - Bethell, Frank, Simpson Memorial Institute, 1949 (Box 2)
    - Beuder, Leonard F., Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation (Box 2)
    - Beutler, Frederick J., Aeronautical Engineering, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Beyer, Robert E., Zoology, 1966 (Box 2)
    - Bhattacharya, Sudipto, Business Administration, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Bidelman, William, Astronomy, 1964 (Box 2)
      (nb 76)
    - Bidlack, Russell E., Library Science, 1957, 1983, 1977, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Bierbaum, Rosina, Natural Resources, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Bierly, Eugene W., Civil Engineering, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Bigelow, Wilbur C., Chemical and Metallurgical Engineering, 1960, 1978, 1983, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Bike, Stacy, Chemical Engineering, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Bilik, Jerry H., Music, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Binder, Kurt C., Engineering Graphis, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Bingley, John E., Office of Student Affairs; History, 1954, 1962 (Box 2)
      (na 113)
    - Birch, Joseph David, Psychology, 1959, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Bird, Waldo H., Psychiatry, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Birdsall, Theodore G., Electrical Engineering, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Birkerts, Gunnar G., Architecture, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Bishop, Robert L., Journalism, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Bishop, Susan, Business Administration, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Biss, Ken, Electrical Engineering, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Bissell, R. Ward, History of Art, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Bitondo, Dominic, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Bixby, $55 Million Program, 1965 (Box 2)
    - Bixler, Debbie, Eng. Placement, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Bizek, Barbara (SEE: Hopwood Winners), Hopwood Winner (Box 2)
    - Bjork, Robert A., 1967 (Box 2)
    - Black, Caesar, English, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Black, Fred I., School of Business Administration, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Black, Gregory, University Club, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Black, Richard, Architecture and Design, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Black, Thomas J., Engineering Drawing, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Blackburn, Estelle, Barbour Gymnasium, 1946 (Box 2)
      (na 116-117)
    - Blackburn, Robert, Higher Education, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Blackett, Olin W., Business Administration, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Blackstone, Jerry, Music, 1988 (Box 2)
    - Blaha, Arlene, Nursing, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Blake, Caesar, English, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Blasi, Vincent, Law, 1980, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Blatt, Josef, Music, 1958, 1973, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Bleekman, George M., Engineering, 1962 (Box 2)
    - Bleuer, Jeanne, Education, 1984 (Box 2)
    - Blicke, Frederick F., Pharmaceutical Chemistry, 1959 (Box 2)
    - Blikken, Wendel, Electrical Engineering, 1963 (Box 2)
    - Bliss, Frances B., ISR, 1961 (Box 2)
    - Block, Roxanna, Office of Administrative Systems, 1985, 1981 (Box 2)
    - Blonly, Senator, 1953 (Box 2)
    - Blood, Robert O., Jr., Sociology, 1960 (Box 2)
    - Bloome, David, Education, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Bloomer, Henry Harlan, Speech, 1953, 1954, 1958, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Blotner, Joseph, English, 1975, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Blotner, Yvonne, 1975 (Box 2)
    - Blouin, Francis X., Bentley Library; Library Science, 1981 (Box 2)
    - Blumberg, Leonard U., 1951 (Box 2)
    - Boak, Arthur, Ancient History (Box 2)
    - Boardman, Thomas, Industrial Engineering, 1976 (Box 2)